

CONTACT

- Phone
 - +1 647-291-3233
- 📥 Emai
 - kalvinson910210@gmail.com
 - Location
- 4417 Victoria Park Ave, Toronto,
 Ontario in Canada
- Enter Birth Date

GITHUB



Click On Icon

https://github.com/KalvinSon

SKILLS

- React
- Vue

Angular

Node.js

PHP

Laravel

HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript

Blockchain

Kalvin Son

Profession



SUMMARY

A PROBLEM SOLVER and TECHNOLOGY ENTHUSIAST is how I can be described the best. With almost 5 years of experience in Blockchain Domain & more than 10 years of experience in Web,I have worked with various of the use-cases in it and have delivered a number of enterprise grade products.

Having an unconventional career graph, I believe that 'SkillSet' and 'Talent' should always be the key factors to look for in an individual.

I have played a key role in turning startup companies into bigger ones and have had successful track records in a fast growing startup environment.



EXPERIENCE

Senior Blockchain developer

Senior Blockchain developer

iii 2021.08~2022.07

 460 Saint-Catherine St W #305, Montreal, QC H3B 1A6, Canada

460 Saint-Catherine St W #305, Montreal, QC H3B 1A6, Canada

- Develop token contract with complex distribution (token minted via call function and time lock
- Develop a launchpad involving allocation distribution
- Develop a staking platform
- Develop swap exchange (fork and twist) and liquidity mining pool Develop dashboard linked all platform information

Blockchain developer / Senior Web Developer Chimpare Designs Limited

- Solent Business Park, 4500 Parkway, Whiteley, Fareham P015 7AZ, UK
- Technical assistance and consultation at the idea initiation stage.
- Smart contract development and deployment for getting Raptor token out.
- Development of Cryptocurrency system with Raptor Token and Wallet.
- Developed some modules of Gosama platform such as customer loyalty system using MEAN stack.

Senior Full Stack Engineer (MEAN & MERN) **Deligence Technologies PVT. LTD**

ii 2015.03~2018.01

- 106-107, First floor, Jyoti Shikar Tower, District Center, Janakpuri, New Delhi, 110058, India
- React/ React hook / Material UI front-end web application for real estate tax calculation
- Collaborate with the Ruby, TypeScript, Vue and React stack
- Closely collaborate with the lead team designer to implement new features in the design system
- Streamline Webforms' UI documentation in isolation for Storybook
- Update Storybook styled components for isolated documentation Fix and update Ul's bugs in Webforms

Powered by: \$0

SKILLS

Mobile App

SOL

NonSQL

DevOps

LANGUAGES

English





EXPERIENCE

Senior Front-End Engineer (AngularJS), Senior Front-End Engineer (AngularJS),

iii 2014.01~2015.02

- Unit No 5&6, Fourth Floor of Annexe Block Tower-B, Stellar IT Park, C-25, Sector 62, Noida, Uttar Pradesh 201307, India
- Angular/rxjs/ angular-material web app for managing user registration for seminar and webinars hosting in firebase
- Node.js backend firebase cloud function with firestore as database and google storage as file storage
- Took 100% responsibility of the project of planning, architecting, developing and deploying

Front-End Development Engineer (Vue.js), **Long View Systems**

- · Built several vue.js web applications for VR products
- Used different UI frameworks like Ant design or Vuetify based on project
- · Integrated headless CSM, Butter CMS for pulling data and assets



EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Computer and Information Science

University of British Columbia, BC

- Obtained First Class with Distinction in all the semesters
- Earned the accolade, "Best Outgoing Student Academics" for the year 2013

Powered by: 🚊